# Nathan S Jang

# Software Engineer

Permanent Resident of U.S.

#### **SUMMARY**

Software Engineer with a background in the Michelin starred culinary scene for over 8 years. I am a self starter who is a reliable and responsible individual, having experience in high pressure and fast paced working environments, successfully producing finest quality end results. I have a strong passion for learning, maintaining, and improving complex systems.

## **PROJECTS**

# **KUSAKABE** (github) — React, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose

Make an online order MERN stack app for famous Omakase restaurant named 'KUSAKABE' using React, MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, Material UI

# Calculator (github) — React, Codesandbox

During the React hackathon, built a simple calculator with other developers using React and Codesandbox

# Nathan's recipe blog (github) — MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, Google-OAuth, Material Design

Make recipe sites from my experience using MongoDB, Mongoose, Express, Google-OAuth and Material design for styling

## Minesweeper (github) — HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Simple Minesweeper Game using HTML, CSS, Java Script

### **EXPERIENCE**

# **The Shota**, San Francisco, CA — Sushi & Kitchen Chef

MAR 2019 - MAR 2020

Trained and supervised new staff members as well as managing and leading the team. Ensure highest quality and timely delivery of course of the meal.

# **Kusakabe**, San Francisco, CA — Sushi & Kitchen Chef

OCT 2016 - MAR 2019

Being promoted after 3 months of learning, served as a sushi & kitchen chef in an Omakase (Chef's Prix Fixe Menu) restaurant serving Sushi-in-Kaiseki style. Successfully led the team in a face paced and a high pressured environment.

Walnut Creek, CA 94597 (415) 317-5944 nathan.s.jang@gmail.com https://nathansjang.github.io/Portfolio/ linkedin.com/in/nathan-sb-j github.com/NathanSJang

#### **SKILLS**

## Languages

HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Python

## **Databases and Frameworks**

React | Express | MongoDB | Mongoose | Material design

#### Tools

Figma | Trello

### **EDUCATION**

## **General Assembly**

**Software Engineering Immersive** San Francisco, CA

12 weeks of full-time coding bootcamp in Software Engineering program running from October 2020 to February 2021

Recognized and voted as "The most elegant coder"

## California Culinary Academy

**Culinary Arts**San Francisco, CA

### **LANGUAGES**

English, Korean